http://www.uwcad.it/cookie-policy

X
Scholarships
Hit "BOOK NOW" to book your hotel and make a cost-free donation to UWC Adriatic or read more.
Cookie policy
The methods used in web site administration in relation to processing of site users’ personal data are described below.
This notice is provided in accordance with art. 13 of Legislative Decree no. 196 of June 30, 2003 (hereafter referred to as the Privacy Code) to all those who interact with the site’s web services (excluding external web sites linked on the site).
This notice is also inspired by Recommendation no. 2/2001 of the European Personal Data Protection Authorities, combined in the Group set up under art. 29 of Directive no. 95/46/EC, adopted on May 17, 2001 to identify certain minimum requirements for on-line personal data collection.
Data controller
Data on identified or identifiable persons may be obtained during use of this web site.
The data controller is the owner of the site, as identified at the bottom of each page on the site.
Data processing location
Data connected with this site’s web services is processed at the location identified below, and is processed only by the persons in charge of data processing. No personal data from the web service will be disclosed. The personal data supplied by users is used exclusively for the purposes of providing the service requested and will be disclosed to third parties only if strictly necessary for this purpose.
Types of data processed
1) Browsing data
Information systems and software procedures used in the functioning of this web site acquire certain items of personal data in the course of their regular operations, the transmission of which is implicit in the use of the Internet based on the TCP/IP protocol. This is information which is not collected to be associated with identified data subjects, but which could, due to its nature, permit identification of users browsing the site through processing and association with data held by third parties. This category of data includes "IP addresses" or domain names of computers used by users connecting to the site, addresses of requested resources in URI (Uniform Resource Identifier) notation, the time of the request, the method used to submit the request to the web server, the size of the file obtained in response, the numerical code identifying the status of the response given by the web server (success, error, etc…) and other parameters on the user’s operating system and computing environment. This data will be used solely in order to obtain anonymous statistical information on
site use and to check that the web site is functioning properly. Note that data of this type may be used to determine responsibility in the event of computer crimes damaging the web site or other connected or related web sites; other than in this case, data on web contacts is not currently held for more than a few days.
2) Data supplied voluntarily by the user
Requests to send e-mail to addresses indicated in the appropriate section of this web site result in acquisition of certain personal data on the person submitting the request, including the person’s email address, required to respond to the request.
3) Cookies
Cookies are not used to transmit personal information, and no persistent cookies or systems for tracing users of any kind are employed. Use of so-called session cookies (which are not permanently memorised on the user’s computer and are normally deleted when the browser is closed) is strictly limited to transmission of session identifiers necessary to permit safe, efficient browsing of the site. These session cookies used on this web site do not resort to other forms of information technology which could potentially compromise the confidentiality of users’ browsing and do not acquire personal data identifying the user.
Providing personal data
Apart from the specified cases of browsing data, users are free to provide or not provide the personal data listed in electronic request forms in the section of the web site for requesting particular services. Failure to provide this data may, however, make it impossible to fulfil the request.
Data processing methods and security measures
Personal data is processed using automated and other tools solely for the amount of time strictly necessary to achieve the purposes for which the data is collected. Specific security measures are applied to prevent loss of data, unlawful or incorrect use and unauthorised access.
Data subjects' rights
Data subjects of the personal data collected as described in the above sections are entitled to obtain confirmation of the existence or non-existence of data on them at any time and to know their content and origin, check their accuracy and request integration, updating or correction of the data under art. 7 of the Privacy Code.
The data subject is entitled to request deletion or transformation into anonymous form of the data and to object to processing of data with legitimate reason.
Requests of this type should be sent by post or email to the address shown at the bottom of this page.
COOKIE POLICY
This site is committed to protecting your privacy and developing new technologies for offering you new online experiences which are increasingly secure and interesting. Under art. 13 of Legislative Decree 196/2003, “Protection of persons and other parties in relation to processing of personal data”, we provide the following information.
Consent to data processing
By continuing to browse our web site, you agree to the use of cookies in accordance with this notice. If you do not agree with the use of cookies, please disable them, following the instructions appearing in this notice, so that cookies present on our web site will not be installed on your device (PC, tablet, etc.).
Use of cookies
Our web site uses cookies. Cookies are small data files created during browsing, stored by your browser and sent back to our web site whenever you connect again.
We only use technical and analytic cookies. We do not use profiling cookies, which attempt to monitor and profile users during browsing, studying their habits and preferences in use of the web in order to send them customised advertising messages.
• Technical cookies are necessary to ensure the correct functioning of certain areas in the web site.
They include both permanent and session cookies. Without these cookies the site or some of its parts may not work properly. Cookies in this category are always sent by our domain.
• Analytic cookies are used to collect information on site use. They provide the basis for statistical analyses, improvement and simplification of site functioning, and monitoring of correct functioning.
These cookies collect information in anonymous form on users’ activities on the site, how they got to the site and the pages they viewed. This site uses the Google Analytics service provided by Google, Inc. to generate statistics on site use; Google Analytics uses cookies which do not memorise personal data. The information that may be obtained from cookies on web site use by users (including IP addresses) will be sent to Google and deposited on the company’s servers.
Google provides this site with data in aggregate form and never in connection with users’ identity, in reports and other IT services. Google does not disclose this information to third parties unless required to do so by law, or unless the third parties are parties who process data for Google. In all cases, Google declares in its notice that it will not associate IP addresses with any other data in its possession.
To consult Google’s privacy notice on the Google Analytics service, go to the Internet site http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html
• our web site also contains third party cookies, which are cookies from other web sites contained in various elements hosted on our pages (social network icons allowing users to interact with social networks, images, videos). Cookies of this type are sent by the domains of the web sites offering the functions present on the site, and are not therefore added to or read by this site. Third parties may use the data collected for their own purposes. For more information on cookies of this type and how they are used by each of the third parties in question, use the links appearing below.
Facebook https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/
Google+ http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/
YouTube http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/(Google privacy policy also applicable to YouTube services)
Linkedin https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy?trk=hb_ft_priv
Pinterest https://about.pinterest.com/it/privacy-policy
Flickr https://policies.yahoo.com/us/en/yahoo/privacy/products/flickr/index.htm
Tumblr https://www.tumblr.com/policy/en/privacy
Twitter https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=it
Delicious https://delicious.com/privacy
Disabling cookies
It is not necessary to ask for users’ express consent to the use of technical and analytic cookies.
Conscious use of this site implies consent to processing of your data for the purposes identified in the notice.
Users can, however, deny their consent to the use of certain cookies. Browsing of our web site may continue normally, but as a number of functions will no longer be active, problems may be encountered in certain other situations, such as use of e-commerce web sites.
Use of various types of cookies may be disabled by selecting the appropriate setting in your browser, which allows you to reject cookies or delete them at the end of each session. Links to instructions on how to disable cookies in the most common browsers are provided below.
Internet Explorer: http://windows.microsoft.com/it-IT/windows7/Block-enable-or-allow-cookies
Google Chrome: https://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=it-IT&answer=95647&p=cpn_cookies
Mozilla Firefox: http://support.mozilla.org/it/kb/Bloccare%20i%20cookie?redirectlocale=en-US&redirectslug=Blocking+cookies
Apple Safari: http://support.apple.com/it-it/HT1677
You may specifically disable only Google Analytics cookies using the additional opt-out component supplied by Google free of charge for the main browsers.
Contact information
If you require any further information on this notice, please contact us at the e-mail address appearing at the foot of the pages on the web site.
Below is a link to “Identification of simplified methods for notice and acquisition of consent to the use of cookies” dated May 8 2014 [doc web n. 3118884]
The methods used in web site administration in relation to processing of site users’ personal data are described below.
This notice is provided in accordance with art. 13 of Legislative Decree no. 196 of June 30, 2003 (hereafter referred to as the Privacy Code) to all those who interact with the site’s web services (excluding external web sites linked on the site).
This notice is also inspired by Recommendation no. 2/2001 of the European Personal Data Protection Authorities, combined in the Group set up under art. 29 of Directive no. 95/46/EC, adopted on May 17, 2001 to identify certain minimum requirements for on-line personal data collection.
Data controller
Data on identified or identifiable persons may be obtained during use of this web site.
The data controller is the owner of the site, as identified at the bottom of each page on the site.
Data processing location
Data connected with this site’s web services is processed at the location identified below, and is processed only by the persons in charge of data processing. No personal data from the web service will be disclosed. The personal data supplied by users is used exclusively for the purposes of providing the service requested and will be disclosed to third parties only if strictly necessary for this purpose.
Types of data processed
1) Browsing data
Information systems and software procedures used in the functioning of this web site acquire certain items of personal data in the course of their regular operations, the transmission of which is implicit in the use of the Internet based on the TCP/IP protocol. This is information which is not collected to be associated with identified data subjects, but which could, due to its nature, permit identification of users browsing the site through processing and association with data held by third parties. This category of data includes "IP addresses" or domain names of computers used by users connecting to the site, addresses of requested resources in URI (Uniform Resource Identifier) notation, the time of the request, the method used to submit the request to the web server, the size of the file obtained in response, the numerical code identifying the status of the response given by the web server (success, error, etc…) and other parameters on the user’s operating system and computing environment. This data will be used solely in order to obtain anonymous statistical information on
site use and to check that the web site is functioning properly. Note that data of this type may be used to determine responsibility in the event of computer crimes damaging the web site or other connected or related web sites; other than in this case, data on web contacts is not currently held for more than a few days.
2) Data supplied voluntarily by the user
Requests to send e-mail to addresses indicated in the appropriate section of this web site result in acquisition of certain personal data on the person submitting the request, including the person’s email address, required to respond to the request.
3) Cookies
Cookies are not used to transmit personal information, and no persistent cookies or systems for tracing users of any kind are employed. Use of so-called session cookies (which are not permanently memorised on the user’s computer and are normally deleted when the browser is closed) is strictly limited to transmission of session identifiers necessary to permit safe, efficient browsing of the site. These session cookies used on this web site do not resort to other forms of information technology which could potentially compromise the confidentiality of users’ browsing and do not acquire personal data identifying the user.
Providing personal data
Apart from the specified cases of browsing data, users are free to provide or not provide the personal data listed in electronic request forms in the section of the web site for requesting particular services. Failure to provide this data may, however, make it impossible to fulfil the request.
Data processing methods and security measures
Personal data is processed using automated and other tools solely for the amount of time strictly necessary to achieve the purposes for which the data is collected. Specific security measures are applied to prevent loss of data, unlawful or incorrect use and unauthorised access.
Data subjects' rights
Data subjects of the personal data collected as described in the above sections are entitled to obtain confirmation of the existence or non-existence of data on them at any time and to know their content and origin, check their accuracy and request integration, updating or correction of the data under art. 7 of the Privacy Code.
The data subject is entitled to request deletion or transformation into anonymous form of the data and to object to processing of data with legitimate reason.
Requests of this type should be sent by post or email to the address shown at the bottom of this page.
COOKIE POLICY
This site is committed to protecting your privacy and developing new technologies for offering you new online experiences which are increasingly secure and interesting. Under art. 13 of Legislative Decree 196/2003, “Protection of persons and other parties in relation to processing of personal data”, we provide the following information.
Consent to data processing
By continuing to browse our web site, you agree to the use of cookies in accordance with this notice. If you do not agree with the use of cookies, please disable them, following the instructions appearing in this notice, so that cookies present on our web site will not be installed on your device (PC, tablet, etc.).
Use of cookies
Our web site uses cookies. Cookies are small data files created during browsing, stored by your browser and sent back to our web site whenever you connect again.
We only use technical and analytic cookies. We do not use profiling cookies, which attempt to monitor and profile users during browsing, studying their habits and preferences in use of the web in order to send them customised advertising messages.
• Technical cookies are necessary to ensure the correct functioning of certain areas in the web site.
They include both permanent and session cookies. Without these cookies the site or some of its parts may not work properly. Cookies in this category are always sent by our domain.
• Analytic cookies are used to collect information on site use. They provide the basis for statistical analyses, improvement and simplification of site functioning, and monitoring of correct functioning.
These cookies collect information in anonymous form on users’ activities on the site, how they got to the site and the pages they viewed. This site uses the Google Analytics service provided by Google, Inc. to generate statistics on site use; Google Analytics uses cookies which do not memorise personal data. The information that may be obtained from cookies on web site use by users (including IP addresses) will be sent to Google and deposited on the company’s servers.
Google provides this site with data in aggregate form and never in connection with users’ identity, in reports and other IT services. Google does not disclose this information to third parties unless required to do so by law, or unless the third parties are parties who process data for Google. In all cases, Google declares in its notice that it will not associate IP addresses with any other data in its possession.
To consult Google’s privacy notice on the Google Analytics service, go to the Internet site http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html
• our web site also contains third party cookies, which are cookies from other web sites contained in various elements hosted on our pages (social network icons allowing users to interact with social networks, images, videos). Cookies of this type are sent by the domains of the web sites offering the functions present on the site, and are not therefore added to or read by this site. Third parties may use the data collected for their own purposes. For more information on cookies of this type and how they are used by each of the third parties in question, use the links appearing below.
Facebook https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/
Google+ http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/
YouTube http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/(Google privacy policy also applicable to YouTube services)
Linkedin https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy?trk=hb_ft_priv
Pinterest https://about.pinterest.com/it/privacy-policy
Flickr https://policies.yahoo.com/us/en/yahoo/privacy/products/flickr/index.htm
Tumblr https://www.tumblr.com/policy/en/privacy
Twitter https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=it
Delicious https://delicious.com/privacy
Disabling cookies
It is not necessary to ask for users’ express consent to the use of technical and analytic cookies.
Conscious use of this site implies consent to processing of your data for the purposes identified in the notice.
Users can, however, deny their consent to the use of certain cookies. Browsing of our web site may continue normally, but as a number of functions will no longer be active, problems may be encountered in certain other situations, such as use of e-commerce web sites.
Use of various types of cookies may be disabled by selecting the appropriate setting in your browser, which allows you to reject cookies or delete them at the end of each session. Links to instructions on how to disable cookies in the most common browsers are provided below.
Internet Explorer: http://windows.microsoft.com/it-IT/windows7/Block-enable-or-allow-cookies
Google Chrome: https://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=it-IT&answer=95647&p=cpn_cookies
Mozilla Firefox: http://support.mozilla.org/it/kb/Bloccare%20i%20cookie?redirectlocale=en-US&redirectslug=Blocking+cookies
Apple Safari: http://support.apple.com/it-it/HT1677
You may specifically disable only Google Analytics cookies using the additional opt-out component supplied by Google free of charge for the main browsers.
Contact information
If you require any further information on this notice, please contact us at the e-mail address appearing at the foot of the pages on the web site.
Below is a link to “Identification of simplified methods for notice and acquisition of consent to the use of cookies” dated May 8 2014 [doc web n. 3118884]
In accordance with Council Directive 93/119/EC, we inform you that this site uses cookies. By continuing to browse the site, you are agreeing to our use of cookies.
OK
Further information
edit
risorsa
